Sergio Penagos

Cra. 1 #43b Sur-23, Bogotá, Bogotá | 3229206546 sergiopenagos881@gmail.com

Summary

A passionate front end developer with 4 years of experience in helping companies and startups develop user-friendly web applications for multiple clients. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Vue plus modern libraries and frameworks and well-versed in Scrum.

Experience

Vass | Bogotá, Bogota

V2 Analyst Programmer | 08/2021 - Present

Create and maintance Vue is Components.

Creating modular, responsive websites using modern Sass techniques and Vue libraries.

Building stable and maintainable codebases using Vue.

Dolphin Enginering | Bogota, bogota

Front End Developer | 03/2021 - 06/2021

Translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/Sass and JavaScript.

Created HTML email templates.

Intevo (Pc Smart) | Bogota, Bogotá

Front End Developer | 12/2019 - 03/2021

Creating new features, functionality and capabilities on the website and app DeOne using React-native, Laravel 7, Ajax, Vue (Vuex), TypeScript, Sass and JSON.

Develop and implementing HTML email templates.

Building stable and maintainable codebases using Vue.

Soulmedical | Bogotá, Bogota

Website Developer | 05/2019 - 11/2019

Translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript.

Created front-end and back-end prototype for a medical billing web platform.

Developed HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Php pages for user interaction.

ConexTravel | Bogota, Bogota

Website Developer | 10/2017 - 12/2018

Created custom React components for internal framework.

Translated design team's UX wireframes and mockups into responsive, interactive features, using HTML/CSS and JavaScript.

Built single-page applications with JavaScript on a custom-built framework.

Skills

English, Javascript, JIRA, APIS, Html5, GIT, CSS

Education

Servicio nacional de Aprendizaje | Bogotá, Bogotá

Associate Degree: Technical Software Developer | 11/2019

• Currently completing courses in technical software developer.

Servicio nacional de aprendizaje | Bogota, Bogotá Associate Degree: Information Systems Analysis Technologist | 09/2022